spieleundwin.com 2012-04-18

# Play free Scratch games and Lottery at SpieleUndWin.com | Do you Scratch?

---  
  
Privacy   
  
At NG International LTD, we are committed to respecting your privacy on our Website(s). We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we acquire when you use Website(s) and the NG International LTD Services. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of our information collection procedures. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:   
support@SpieleUndWin.com

How Do I Agree to the Privacy Policy?   

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of NG International LTD's End User License Agreement. Accordingly, when you check the "I Accept" button or access or use the SPIELE UND WIN Website, you automatically agree to our collection, use, and disclosure of your confidential information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the SPIELE UND WIN Website and/or any NG International LTD Services. 

What Types of Information Does SPIELE UND WIN Collect From its Users?   

Personal Information - We collect Personal Information from Our Users which can be used to easily identify Our Users individually, such as the User's name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information.

Non-Personal Information - We also collect "non-personal" information from Our Users which cannot be readily accessed, and is necessary to personally identify Our Users, such Non-Personal Information to include types of internet browsers, URLs of previous websites visited, ISP and operating systems, and IP Addresses. 

How and When Does SPIELE UND WIN Collect Personal and Non-Personal Information?   

Providing Information to Us – When you create a Player Account on our Website we collect Personal and Non-Personal Information, including your name, email address, financial information and other information required for the registration process. 

Communications With Us - If you communicate with us regarding the Website or the NG International LTD Services, we will collect and retain any information that you provide to us in any such communication(s). 

Analytic and Reporting Technologies - Like the operators of most websites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, click stream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and the NG International LTD Services are accessed. 

Third Party advertisement companies - We run conversion scripts provided by third party advertisement companies to record Non-Personal Information in order to collect statistics regarding the number of users who visit our site in the scope of advertisement campaigns. 

How Does SPIELE UND WIN Use Personal and Non-Personal Information?   

Personal Information - Your Personal Information collected by us is kept strictly confidential and is processed for the purposes of providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the NG International LTD Services and the Website by NG International LTD and/or NG International LTD Partners, such as for verifying your identity, processing your payments, your deposit and/or cash out methods, accepting deposits, sending out cash-out checks, and providing member support. Your Personal Information is also processed by NG International LTD and may be processed by NG International LTD Partners for the purposes of communicating promotional and informational materials. We may be obliged to disclose your Personal Information under law, statute, regulation, or as requested by a governmental authority. 

SPIELE UND WIN will keep your Winning and cash-out information strictly private and confidential and does not provide this information to any third party unless acting under a good faith belief that such information is required to be disclosed under law, regulation or any governmental or competent regulatory authority. Notwithstanding, SPIELE UND WIN may publicize certain details regarding the Winnings for marketing and promotional purposes as more fully set out in the Terms of Use. 

Non-Personal Information - We use non-personal information to track your use of the SPIELE UND WIN Website and for other internal purposes, in particular to provide for, maintain, evaluate, and improve the SPIELE UND WIN Services and the Website. 

Can I "Opt Out" From Receiving Promotional Communications?   

You may "opt-out" from receiving promotional communications at any time. To "opt out," please let us know by sending a blank message with the word "remove" to support@SpieleUndWin.com or to the email address provided in the promotional communication from the NG International LTD Partner. 

What about Cookies?   

A cookie is a message that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the SPIELE UND WIN Website, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and allow you to sign in easily and begin playing SPIELE UND WIN Games quickly when you visit the Website. 

How Can I Review and Make Changes to My Personal Information?   

You can review and modify your Personal information at the SPIELE UND WIN Website at any time by clicking on the 'UPDATE ACCOUNT' button from the cashier. You can also request that we correct errors in your Personal Information by emailing us at support@SpieleUndWin.com. 

For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity. If you wish, we will delete all of your Personal Information (except for your transaction history and other data that we are required to keep under applicable laws) from our records upon your request. However, if you choose to delete your Personal Information, you may not be able to access some areas of the Website or use some of the SPIELE UND WIN Services. 

How Does SPIELE UND WIN Protect My Personal Information?   

Personal Information - we use only the best, up to date, methods to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access or disclosure. All Personal Information is transferred from and to our Website using the latest encryption technologies (SSL). Whenever we obtain Personal Information we use the most suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to secure such Personal Information. SPIELE UND WIN maintains a highly secure server possessing the latest Firewall technologies available in today's marketplace, and we are committed to constantly updating our security systems with the latest products concerning online security. 

What do you think?   

We welcome your questions and comments regarding our Privacy Policy. Please send us an e-mail to support@SpieleUndWin.com.
